{
    "subject": "Cynthia_Stone",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Jack_Lemmon",
    "human_readable": "Cynthia Stone is married to Jack Lemmon.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8994144201278687,
            "question": "Is Cynthia Stone married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.897473931312561,
            "question": "To whom is Cynthia Stone married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8696087598800659,
            "question": "Who is married to Jack Lemmon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8654949069023132,
            "question": "What relationship exists between Cynthia Stone and Jack Lemmon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.855866014957428,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Cynthia Stone and Jack Lemmon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7964619994163513,
            "question": "Who are Jack Lemmon and Cynthia Stone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.654821515083313,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the marriage of Jack Lemmon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5855046510696411,
            "question": "What is the name of Jack Lemmon's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5752326846122742,
            "question": "What is the name of Jack Lemmon's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12926390767097473,
            "question": "Name one famous person married to another famous person."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Cynthia Stone is married to Jack Lemmon.",
            "html": "yago_14003_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Jack Lemmon's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_14003_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Jack Lemmon's wife?",
            "html": "yago_14003_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about the marriage of Jack Lemmon?",
            "html": "yago_14003_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14003_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14003_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14003_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14003_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14003_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14003_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14003_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14003_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14003_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14003_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After evaluating the context information, I found that:\n\n* The first document mentions \"Jack Lemmon and Cynthia Stone were married for 5 years.\"\n* The second document lists Jack Lemmon as a husband of Cynthia Stone under her biography.\n* The third document confirms that Cynthia Stone was previously married to Cliff Robertson (1957 - 1960) and Jack Lemmon (1950 - 1956).\n\nTherefore, the information in the documents supports the triple.\n\nResponse: {'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Cynthia Stone is married to Jack Lemmon.\" The details in multiple files indicate their marriage from 1950 to 1956, although they later divorced. However, for the given query about their marital status without specifying the timeframe or stating it as a past event, the information provided does affirm that they were indeed married to each other."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}